mysoapbox.com 2013-12-19

# MySoapBox: Privacy Policy

ISA and SoapBoxSample™ (collectively, 'us', 'we', 'Operators') have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy for the website www.mysoapbox.com. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices and how we treat your personal information when you visit our website and use our services. 

Your privacy is very important to us. Because we gather certain types of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") from users of our website and for various business activities and operational purposes, we feel you should know how we collect, use, disclose, manage, and store the Personal Information that you may voluntarily provide us and the Personal Information that is collected passively through the use of cookies or image tags on our website. This Privacy Policy is a part of the Site's [Terms and Conditions](http://www.mysoapbox.com/page/6), which is binding on all Site users.

Questions regarding our privacy policy may be submitted to [support@mysoapbox.com](mailto:support@mysoapbox.com). If you choose to write us an e-mail, please reference the Privacy Policy in your subject line. MySoapBox™ will attempt to respond to all reasonable concerns and inquiries in a timely manner.  Our corporate mailing address if you wish to use regular mail is:

_MySoapBox  
15400 Sherman Way, Fourth Floor  
Van Nuys, CA 91406, USA_

This privacy policy, effective October 23, 2012 applies to all users of the Website and MySoapBox services.

**INFORMATION COLLECTED  
**

We do not collect any Personal Information from you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. We invite users to register and opt-in as members of our panel for the purpose of taking market research surveys.   When you sign up to become a MySoapBox panel member, you are asked to submit Personal Information during registration. Demographic information can be submitted during registration or at a later time and may be asked during surveys for research purposes.  Once you opt in as a panel member, you may also voluntarily submit survey responses which are also captured and stored.  

The following personal information collected includes but are not limited to First and Last name, Residential or Work address, Email address, Telephone number, Race , Age/Gender, and Date of birth.

The following demographic information collected includes but are not limited to, Income, Disabilities, Educational attainment, Home ownership, Employment status, Hobbies, interests, product use/ownership and Geographic Location.

Our servers may automatically collect certain non-personal, log-file information about your use of the Website whenever you access the Website. Information collected includes, but is not limited to your Internet browser, operating system, internet source such as PC, tablet, or mobile, the domain name of your ISP, your click areas on the website, time and date visited, length of time on the website,  and the third-party web sites or advertisements linked to or from the Website that you visited. When you use or visit the Website, our servers log your IP address.

We shall collect IP addresses for the purposes of providing our services, including, without limitation, system administration, troubleshooting, user compliance with our terms of service, investigating security breaches, and compiling non-personal information such as how many visitors logged on to the Website.

We also use this information for security purposes, such as to detect and to block security breaches, and to detect violations of our quality standards, for example, detecting multiple survey responses from the same user. Cookies are small text files stored on your computer by a website that assigns a numerical user ID and stores certain information about your online browsing. When we use cookies, we do so to help us recognize you as a prior user of this site and for survey resumption if you choose to suspend your survey to resume at a later date. The cookie file does not store your personal information. If you prefer not to receive cookies from our website you can disable their use in your browser settings. By doing so you may reduce the functionality of the web pages you view.

**HOW IS YOUR INFORMATION USED  
**

MySoapBox is not in the business of selling your personally identifiable information. We use the information you may provide to us for the limited purposes described herein. Protecting survey participants' privacy has always been an important part of our business. It is essential that all survey respondents be assured that no personally identifiable information is shared with third parties, other than to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to abide by legal requirements of the United States Government.

MySoapBox adheres to the standards and guidelines laid out by ESOMAR: [www.esomar.org](http://www.esomar.org/) and CASRO: [www.casro.org](http://www.casro.org/) and follows the US law when processing any personal data for the following purposes:

  * to keep you updated and request your views about MySoapBox
  * transferring any personal information to any MySoapBox subsidiary or department (i.e. when you  request information and your request is forwarded to the appropriate group
  * to process any enquiries raised by you and other communications initiated by you about MySoapBox products and services
  * when opted in by you, to send you marketing communications

MySoapBox’s websites may contain links to information on other websites. We do not have any control over these other websites, and therefore we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide while visiting those sites. Those websites are not governed by this privacy policy, and if you have questions about how a website uses your information, consult that site's privacy statement.

Without explicit permission, respondent identity and/or respondent-identifiable information will not be released for anything other than follow-on research use by another research firm or the client's research department. The use of confidential information for targeted sales or marketing efforts is expressly prohibited.

Any personal information provided when participating in an online sweepstakes or other online incentive program we host is used only for the purpose of fulfilling the given prize or incentive.

**OWNERSHIP CHANGE  
**

In the event that another company acquires all or part of MySoapBox, we reserve the right to include any or all Personal Information among the assets transferred to the acquiring company. MySoapBox will require the new owners to agree in writing and protect the security and integrity of the transferred Personal Information in accordance with the applicable laws. We do not guarantee that in the event of a change of ownership, receiving such information in connection with any of these transactions will comply with all the terms of this policy.

**DATA SECURITY**

We employ advanced technology and internal processes to protect the information our members release to us. Additionally, only select, authorized employees have access to the data collected for processing and maintain the database that stores list information.

MySoapBox also safeguards all information collected through its websites from unauthorized access. Only authorized  MySoapBox employees or agents carrying out permitted business functions are allowed to access this information. In addition, each employee of MySoapBox is required to sign a confidentiality agreement requiring him or her to keep confidential all personal information of panel members. Employees who violate the confidentiality agreement are subject to disciplinary actions, including termination when appropriate.

MySoapBox  protects your personal information from unauthorized access, use, disclosure or loss. This site has security measures (including online and offline physical, electronic and managerial safeguards) in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information, including your e-mail address, under our control. As with any transmission over the Internet; however, there is always some element of risk involved in sending personal information online beyond our control. In the unlikely event that MySoapBox suffers a breach of its security systems and an individual or entity gains unauthorized access to any information stored on MySoapBox servers, MySoapBox will immediately investigate the security breach, and will provide prompt notice to any individual whose information was affected.

**UPDATING INFORMATION  
**

We try to provide you with access to your Personal Information in order to make updates, corrections, or deletions through their membership account. We require members to identify themselves by logging in with their credentials.  Any changes are asked to be confirmed prior to being processed.   We may decline to process requests that are deemed repetitive or systematic, jeopardize the privacy of others or are impractical.  Updates must comply with the instructions therein in order to process correctly. 

**OPTING-OUT  
**

If a panelist would like to stop using the products, services, and communications provided by MySoapBox, the panel member may terminate his or her membership by logging in to their account and following the instructions to delete one’s account.  You may also send an email request to [support@mysoapbox.com](mailto:support@mysoapbox.com).  Once opted out, MySoapBox will deactivate the membership account which will result in ending the delivery of survey invites,  Please allow a few weeks for existing invitations to expire. MySoapBox will retain the Personal Information of a terminating member for an indefinite period of time and will continue to comply with the terms of this privacy policy. 

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

MySoapBox complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and all other applicable laws and regulations concerning children and the Internet.

MySoapBox will not knowingly collect information from a child without their parent’s consent. If we become aware that a user of our website is a child who is using this website without the consent of his parent or guardian, we will use reasonable action to delete any information submitted by that child.

If you are a parent or guardian who has discovered that your child has submitted his or her personal information without your consent, MySoapBox will take reasonable steps to remove that information from the its database at your request. To request removal of your child’s information, please send us an e-mail at [support@mysoapbox.com](mailto:support@mysoapbox.com).

**THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES AND ADVERTISEMENTS**

The Website and service content may contain links to third party sites and resources controlled by third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these other sites or resources, and you should consult the privacy statements of the governing sites.

**CHANGES TO THE POLICY**

By agreeing to participate in the MySoapBox market research services, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. MySoapBox reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at its discretion and will post such changes on the Website for you to review.   Your continued participation in the MySoapBox research services after MySoapBox revises this Privacy Policy constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.
